<Attributions>
<Module>
<Name>Test Tilesets</Name>
<URL></URL>
<Description></Description>
<Licenses>
MIT
</Licenses>
</Module>

<Attribution>
<Name>DENZI's 32x32 orthogonal tilesets</Name>
<URL>https://opengameart.org/content/denzis-32x32-orthogonal-tilesets</URL>
<Description>
One of many of Denzi's wonderful pixel art sets. 32x32 pixel 3/4 overhead orthogonal perspective stuff including dungeon tiles, monsters, items, ability icons and more. 

There are other 32x32 pixel orthogonal sprites from Denzi, but I've kept them as separate submissions because they are released under different licenses. 

This may work well with Denzi's other works
Copyright/Attribution Notice: 
DENZI部屋のドット絵フリー素材は、クリエイティブ・コモンズ・ライセンス (http://www3.wind.ne.jp/DENZI/diary/) に基づいて公開しています。（CC-by SA　表示-継承）https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/ ___________________________________________________________________________ Translation: "DENZI Room's pixel art (published at http://www3.wind.ne.jp/DENZI/diary/) is free material under the Creative Commons license (CC-BY-SA attribution, share alike) https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/"

Author: 
DENZI
(Submitted by MedicineStorm)
</Description>
<Licenses>
CC BY-SA 3.0
</Licenses>
<Files>tilesets/denzi_32x32_orthogonal/*</Files>
</Attribution>

<Attribution>
<Name>DENZI's public domain art</Name>
<URL>https://opengameart.org/content/denzis-public-domain-art</URL>
<Description>
One of many of Denzi's wonderful pixel art sets. 3/4 overhead orthogonal perspective stuff including dungeon tiles, monsters, items, ability icons, and more. 

Much of this artwork can also be found in the Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup set, but a lot of really great stuff can be found here that was not included in that set.

Most of this is 32x32 pixel sprites. There are other 32x32 pixel orthogonal sprites from Denzi, but I've kept them as separate submissions because they are released under different licenses. 

This may work well with Denzi's other works

UPDATE: new preview images showing more of what's inside. Also, if you prefer your sprites and tiles as individual files, they're all organized into handy category folders!


Artwork by DENZI
denzi.diary@gmail.com

Originally downloaded from http://www3.wind.ne.jp/DENZI/diary/

Attribution/Licensing:
	Creative Commons Zero: http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/
	Attribution not required, but appreciated: DENZI Room's pixel art http://www3.wind.ne.jp/DENZI/diary/
	
Also available at http://opengameart.org/content/denzis-public-domain-art

DENZI's public domain art
Author: 
DENZI
(Submitted by MedicineStorm)
</Description>
<Licenses>
CC0
</Licenses>
<Files>tilesets/denzi_public_domain/*</Files>
</Attribution>

<Attribution>
<Name>Dungeon Crawl 32x32 tiles</Name>
<URL>https://opengameart.org/content/dungeon-crawl-32x32-tiles</URL>
<Description>
Here are the tiles used in the game Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup http://crawl.develz.org/wordpress/

Package contains over 3000 tiles! This is a collaborative effort from many, many artists. The full list of artists can be found in the package crawl-tiles Oct-5-2010\utility\FilteredList.txt

All images are 2D 32x32 pixel tiles in orthogonal (overhead) three-quarters  perspective. 

Contains things like terrain, walls, decorative dungeon features, monsters, spell effects, items, GUI elements, player avatars, and more!

EDIT: A new supplemental set of over 3000 additional tiles is now available! Check out https://opengameart.org/content/dungeon-crawl-32x32-tiles-supplemental
Copyright/Attribution Notice: 
You can use these tilesets in your program freely. No attribution is required. As a courtesy, include a link to the OGA page: http://opengameart.org/content/dungeon-crawl-32x32-tiles, the crawl-tiles page: http://code.google.com/p/crawl-tiles/ or see the License Notice instructions on http://rltiles.sourceforge.net/

Author: 
Chris Hamons (maintainer)
(Submitted by MedicineStorm)
</Description>
<Licenses>
CC0
</Licenses>
<Files>tilesets/dc_32x32/*</Files>
</Attribution>

<Attribution>
<Name>Dungeon Crawl 32x32 tiles supplemental</Name>
<URL>https://opengameart.org/content/dungeon-crawl-32x32-tiles-supplemental</URL>
<Description>
In addition to the 3000+ original tiles, here are 3000+ MORE tiles used in the game Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup http://crawl.develz.org/wordpress/

The great artists of the Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup team have recently enhanced and added to the already-amazing set with this supplemental collection of tiles: even more spells, effects, monsters, items, GUI elements, player avatars, terrain, and dungeon features.

All images are 2D 32x32 pixel tiles in orthogonal (overhead) three-quarters  perspective.

    Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup Supplemental.zip file contains the latest addition of 3000+ tiles. The tiles are individual 32x32 sprite .png files organized into folder categories. See https://opengameart.org/content/dungeon-crawl-32x32-tiles for the original set of tiles these are meant to supplement.
    Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup Full.zip file contains both the first set plus this newer addition for a total of over 6000 tiles! The tiles are individual 32x32 sprite .png files organized into folder categories.
    ProjectUtumno_supplemental.png file is the same 3000+ found in Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup Supplemental.zip, but arranged in a nice (huge) tileset.
    ProjectUtumno_full.png file is the same 6000+ found in Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup Full.zip, but arranged in a nice (huger) tileset.

Have you ever played Dungeon Crawl Stone Soup? You should. Seriously, it's a great game. These tiles are a collaborative effort of many artists. See README.TXT included in the .zip files for a full list of the contributors.
Copyright/Attribution Notice: 
You can use these tilesets in your program freely. No attribution is required. As a courtesy, include a link to the OGA page: http://opengameart.org/content/dungeon-crawl-32x32-tiles-supplemental, or the crawl-tiles page: https://github.com/crawl/tiles

Author: 
MedicineStorm
</Description>
<Licenses>
CC0
</Licenses>
<Files>tilesets/dc_32x32/*</Files>
</Attribution>

</Attributions>